Guide to the Course and Time Rosters and Course and Room Rosters, 1976-2008.
Course and Time Rosters and Course and Room Rosters,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Course and Time Rosters and Course and Room Rosters, 1976-2008.
36-1-4211
Cornell University. University Registrar.
1 cubic foot
Printed Materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Course and time rosters and course and room rosters published in the fall and spring semesters and also Summer session. Rosters also include academic and examination calendars as well as course instructor.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Course and time rosters and course and room rosters published in the fall and spring semesters and also Summer session. Rosters also include academic and examination calendars as well as course instructor.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University -- Degrees.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Course and Time Rosters and Course and Room Rosters
CONTAINER LIST
- Course and Time Rosters and Course and Room Rosters
  - Fall 1976 Course & Time Roster, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1977 Course & Time Roster, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1978 Course & Room Roster, 1978-01-19 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1978 Course & Room Roster, 1978-08 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1981 Course & Time Roster, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1982 Course & Room Roster, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1983 Course & Room Roster, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1986 Course & Time Roster, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1989 Course and Time Roster, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1990 Course and Time Roster, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1990 Course and Room Roster, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1991 Course and Time Roster, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1991 Course and Room Roster, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1991 Course and Time Roster, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1991 Course and Room Roster, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1992 Course and Time Roster, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1992 Course and Room Roster, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1992 Course and Time Roster, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1992 Course and Room Roster, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1993 Course and Time Roster, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1993 Course and Room Roster, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1993 Course and Time Roster, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1993 Course and Room Roster, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1994 Course and Time Roster, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1994 Course and Room Roster, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1994 Course and Time Roster, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1994 Course and Room Roster, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1995 Course and Time Roster, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1995 Course and Room Roster, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1995 Course and Time Roster, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1995 Course and Time Roster Revised, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1995 Course and Room Roster, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1996 Course and Time Roster, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1996 Course and Room Roster, 1996 (Box 1)
    First issue to include world wide web link for updated information.
  - Fall 1996 Course and Time Roster, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1996 Course and Room Roster, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1997 Course and Time Roster, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1997 Course and Room Roster, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1997 Course and Time Roster, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1997 Course and Room Roster, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1998 Course and Time Roster, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1998 Course and Room Roster, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1998 Course and Time Roster, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1998 Course and Room Roster, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1999 Course and Time Roster, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Spring 1999 Course and Room Roster, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1999 Course and Time Roster, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1999 Course and Room Roster, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2000 Course and Time Roster, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2000 Course and Room Roster, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2000 Course and Time Roster, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2000 Course and Room Roster, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2001 Course and Time Roster, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2001 Course and Room Roster, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2001 Course and Time Roster, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2001 Course and Room Roster, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2002 Course and Time Roster, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2002 Course and Room Roster, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2002 Course and Time Roster, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2002 Course and Room Roster, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2003 Course and Time Roster, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2003 Course and Room Roster, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2003 Course and Time Roster, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2003 Course and Room Roster, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2004 Course and Time Roster, 2004; 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Spring 2004 Course and Room Roster, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2004 Course and Time Roster, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2004 Course and Room Roster, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2005 Course and Time Roster, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2005 Course and Room Roster, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Summer Session 2005 Course and Time Roster, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2005 Course and Time Roster, 2005 (Box 1)
    Incorrectly printed title as ~Course and Room Roster
  - Fall 2005 Course and Room Roster, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2006 Course and Time Roster, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2006 Course and Room Roster, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2006 Course and Time Roster, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2006 Course and Room Roster, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2007 Course and Room Roster, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2007 Course and Room Roster, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2007 Course and Time Roster, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Fall 2007 Course and Time Roster, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2008 Course and Time Roster, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Spring 2008 Course and Room Roster, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Summer Session 2008 Course and Time Roster, 2008 (Box 1)